aelichung@gmail.com (626) 348-9900 anne-elise.me Santa Clara, CA

Combining an architectural background with UX skills to design user-centered experiences.

TOOLS & KNOW-HOW

UX Design

Draw.io, Balsamiq, User flows, User stories

Developer Skills

HTML, CSS, Javascript, C#, jQuery, Firebase, Git

Digital Prototyping/Research

Sketch, Figma, Invision, Usabilityhub, Maze

Adobe CC

Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Lightroom, Premiere

3D Design & Rendering

Unity, AutoCAD, Rhino, SketchUp, Blender, Revit, V-Ray

Physical Prototyping & Mock-ups

3D printing, lasercutting, working with wood/metal/plaster/resin etc.

PROJECTS

DESIGN & DEVELOP Ongoing (2 weeks)

VR Meditation App - Bonsai Gardener Demo

Grow and sculpt your own bonsai tree, in a relaxing virtual environment. Created using Blender and Unity for Google Cardboard and for the web.

More Info: https://anne-elise.me/case-studies/bonsai.html

UX UI & FRONT-END 2018 (8 weeks)

houseplant

An online plant store for people with black thumbs.

I designed, tested, and developed an e-commerce site to help people plant shop confidently.

More Info: https://anne-elise.me/case-studies/houseplant.html

UI & CONSTRUCTION 2015 (10 weeks)

Striptease

I worked in a team of 20 to create a provocative installation, blending both physical and digital design. I lead the design for the user interface, as well as helping with construction and design. The installation show was attended by over a hundred people and warmly received.

More Info (click on the striptease gallery link): https://anne-elise.me/work.html

Video: https://youtu.be/j8MizHxy8-4?t=26s

EDUCATION

DESIGN PROGRAM 2017-present

BACHELOR OF ARCHITECTURE 2010–2015

Bloc

California Polytechnic State University San Luis Obispo

WORK EXPERIENCE

CAD CONSULTANT 2017-present

WDA (Warner Design Associates)

Providing CAD training, project support and technical assistance.

TECHNICAL DESIGNER 2015–2017

EDG Interior Architecture and Design

Worked with construction team, engineers, and clients to create luxury hotels and restaurants.

SERVICE

UX / UI / FRONT-END | 2018-present

TUTOR 2018-present

VP OF EDUCATION

2017-2018

Read Santa Clara **Toastmasters Novato**